Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Articles File
        - Niles Daniel Tambyrajah (Box 19, Folder 2104)
        - Ninian (Box 19, Folder 2105)
        - Nino (Nina, Nunia, or Nonna) (Box 19, Folder 2106)
        - Nin, Bernardino de (Box 19, Folder 2107)
        - Nisbet, Henry (Box 19, Folder 2108)
        - Nitschmann, David (Box 19, Folder 2109)
        - Nobili, Robert (Box 19, Folder 2110)
        - Noble, Robert Turlington (Box 19, Folder 2111)
        - Nobrega, Manoel de (Box 20, Folder 2112)
        - Nommensen, Ludwig Ingwer (Box 20, Folder 2113)
        - North, Frank Mason (Box 20, Folder 2114)
        - Norton, Albert and Mary (Box 20, Folder 2115)
        - Norton, H. Wilbert, Sr. (Box 20, Folder 2116)
        - Nott, Henry (Box 20, Folder 2117)
        - Nott, Samuel and Rosanna (Box 20, Folder 2118)
        - Noyes, Harriett Newell (Box 20, Folder 2119)
        - Nsibambi, Simeon (Box 20, Folder 2120)
        - Ntsikana (Box 20, Folder 2121)
        - Nylander, Gutavus Reinhold (Box 20, Folder 2122)
        - Obookiah, Henry (Box 20, Folder 2123)
        - Occum, Samson (Box 20, Folder 2124)
        - O'Donel, James Louis (Box 20, Folder 2125)
        - Odorico of Pordenone (Box 20, Folder 2126)
        - Oehler, Theodor (Box 20, Folder 2127)
        - officier, Morris (Box 20, Folder 2128)
        - Ofori, Attah (Box 20, Folder 2129)
        - Ohm, Thomas (Box 20, Folder 2130)
        - Oldendorp, G. A. (Box 20, Folder 2131)
        - Oldham, J(oseph) H(ouldsworth) (Box 20, Folder 2132)
        - Oldman, William F. (Box 20, Folder 2133)
        - O'Niell, F. W. S (Box 20, Folder 2134)
        - Oppong, Sampson (Box 20, Folder 2135)
        - Origen (Box 20, Folder 2136)
        - Orchard, Ronald Kenneth (Box 20, Folder 2137)
        - Orimolde, Moses (Box 20, Folder 2138)
        - Orr, J. Edwin (Box 20, Folder 2139)
        - Oshitelu, Josiah olunowo (Box 20, Folder 2140)
        - Otto, Albert (Box 20, Folder 2141)
        - Otto (or Otho) of Bamberg (Box 20, Folder 2142)
        - Oviedo, Andreas (Box 20, Folder 2143)
        - Owen, Walter Edwin (Box 20, Folder 2144)
        - Padilla, Juan (Box 20, Folder 2145)
        - Padwick, constance Evelyn (Box 20, Folder 2146)
        - Paez, Pedro (Box 20, Folder 2147)
        - Pal, Krishna (Box 20, Folder 2148)
        - Palafox Y Mendoza, Juan de (Box 20, Folder 2149)
        - Palladius (Box 20, Folder 2150)
        - Pallotti, Vincent (Box 20, Folder 2151)
        - Pallu, Francois (Box 20, Folder 2152)
        - Pamla, Charles (Box 20, Folder 2153)
        - Pandosy, Charles (Box 20, Folder 2154)
        - Pannikar, Raimndo (Box 20, Folder 2155)
        - Pantaenus (Box 20, Folder 2156)
        - Pao'o (Fao) (Box 20, Folder 2157)
        - Papasarantopoulos, Chrysostom (Box 20, Folder 2158)
        - Papeiha (Box 20, Folder 2159)
        - Paracelsus, Aureolus Theophrastus (Box 20, Folder 2160)
        - Parham, Charles Fox (Box 20, Folder 2161)
        - Parker, Peter (Box 20, Folder 2162)
        - Parrinder, E. Geoffrev (Box 20, Folder 2163)
        - Parrish, Sarah Rebecca (Box 20, Folder 2164)
        - Parrott, J. Grady (Box 20, Folder 2165)
        - Parsons, Levi (Box 20, Folder 2166)
        - Paterson, John (Box 20, Folder 2167)
        - Paton, David (Box 20, Folder 2168)
        - Paton, Frank H. L. (Box 20, Folder 2169)
        - Paton, John Gibson (Box 20, Folder 2170)
        - Paton, william (Box 20, Folder 2171)
        - Patrick (Box 20, Folder 2172)
        - Patteson, John Coleridge (2) (Box 20, Folder 2173)
        - Paucke, Florian (Box 20, Folder 2174)
        - Paul, K(anakarayan) T(iruselvam) (Box 20, Folder 2175)
        - Paul VI (Giovanni Battista Montini) (Box 20, Folder 2176)
        - Paul of the Cross (Paolo Francesco Danei) (Box 20, Folder 2177)
        - Paulinus (Box 20, Folder 2178)
        - Paulius of York (Box 20, Folder 2179)
        - Payne, Ernesr A. (Box 20, Folder 2180)
        - Payeras, Mariano (Box 20, Folder 2181)
        - Peabody, Lucy Waterbury (Box 20, Folder 2182)
        - Pean, Charles (Box 20, Folder 2183)
        - Pearse, Joseph (Box 20, Folder 2184)
        - Peck, Edmund James (Box 20, Folder 2185)
        - Peck, John Mason (Box 20, Folder 2186)
        - Pedraza, Cristobal de (Box 20, Folder 2187)
        - Peery, Refus Benton (Box 20, Folder 2188)
        - Peet, Joseph (Box 20, Folder 2189)
        - Pe a, Montenegro, Alonso de (Box 20, Folder 2190)
        - Pennell, Theodore Leighton (Box 20, Folder 2191)
        - Penzotti, Frannsco G. (Box 20, Folder 2192)
        - Perboyre, Gabriel (Box 20, Folder 2193)
        - Perbal, Albert (Box 20, Folder 2194)
        - Percival, Peter (Box 20, Folder 2195)
        - Perkin, Noel (Box 20, Folder 2196)
        - Perkins, Justin (Box 20, Folder 2197)
        - Pereira, Eduardo Carlos (Box 20, Folder 2198)
        - Perroton, Marie Francoise (Sr. Marie du Mont Carmel) (Box 20, Folder 2199)
        - Peter of Ghent (Pedro de Ghant) (Box 20, Folder 2200)
        - Peter the Venerable (Pierre Maurice de Montboissier) (Box 20, Folder 2201)
        - Peters, George W(ilhelm) (Box 20, Folder 2202)
        - Petersen, Anne-Marie (Box 20, Folder 2203)
        - Petersen, Paul Bernhard (Box 20, Folder 2204)
        - Pethrus Lewi (Box 20, Folder 2205)
        - Petitjean Bernard Thadee (Box 20, Folder 2206)
        - Petitot, Emilie (Box 20, Folder 2207)
        - Petri, Ludwig Adolf (Box 20, Folder 2208)
        - Petrie, Irene (Box 20, Folder 2209)
        - Petter, Rodolphe (Box 20, Folder 2210)
        - Pettitt, George (Box 20, Folder 2211)
        - Pfander, Karl Gottlieb (Box 20, Folder 2212)
        - Pfanner, Franz (Box 20, Folder 2213)
        - Pfeiffer, Edward (Box 20, Folder 2214)
        - Philaret (Vasily Mikhailovich Drozdov) (Box 20, Folder 2215)
        - Philip, John (Box 20, Folder 2216)
        - Phillips, Godfrey Edward (Box 20, Folder 2217)
        - Phillippo, James Mursell (Box 20, Folder 2218)
        - Phillips, Jeremiah (Box 20, Folder 2219)
        - Photius (Box 20, Folder 2220)
        - Picket J(arrell) (Box 20, Folder 2221)
        - Pierce, Robert (Bob) (Box 20, Folder 2222)
        - Pierson, Arthur Tappan (Box 20, Folder 2223)
        - Pietro de la madre di Dio (Box 20, Folder 2224)
        - Piigneau de Behaine Pierre Joseph George (Box 20, Folder 2225)
        - Pike, Kenneth (mentions sister Eunice) (Box 21, Folder 2226)
        - Pilhofer, Georg (Box 21, Folder 2227)
        - Pilkington, George Lawrence (Box 21, Folder 2228)
        - Pinkerton, Robert (Box 21, Folder 2229)
        - Pirminius (Box 21, Folder 2230)
        - Pitkin, Horace Tracy and wife (Box 21, Folder 2231)
        - Pitman, Charles (Box 21, Folder 2232)
        - Pius XI (Ambrogio Damiano Achille Ratti) (Box 21, Folder 2233)
        - Pius XII (Eugenio Maria Giusepe Giovanni Pacelli) (Box 21, Folder 2234)
        - Planque, Augustine (Box 21, Folder 2235)
        - Plasencia, Juan de (Box 21, Folder 2236)
        - Plath, Karl H. Chr. (Box 21, Folder 2237)
        - Platt, W. J. (Box 21, Folder 2238)
        - Plutschau, Heinrich (Box 21, Folder 2239)
        - Plymire, Victor Guy (Box 21, Folder 2240)
        - Pompallier, Jean Baptiste Francois (Box 21, Folder 2241)
        - Podmaniczky, Pal (Box 21, Folder 2242)
        - Polding, John Bede (Box 21, Folder 2243)
        - Polhill, Cecil H. (Box 21, Folder 2244)
        - Pollard, Samuel (Box 21, Folder 2245)
        - Polman, Gerrit R. (Box 21, Folder 2246)
        - Pomare II (Box 21, Folder 2247)
        - Ponziglione, Paul Mary (Box 21, Folder 2248)
        - Pope, George Uglow (Box 21, Folder 2249)
        - Popley, H. A. (Box 21, Folder 2250)
        - Porres, Martin de (Box 21, Folder 2251)
        - Porter, Lucins Chapin (Box 21, Folder 2252)
        - Posnett, Charles Walker (Box 21, Folder 2253)
        - Pott, F. L. Hawks (Box 21, Folder 2254)
        - Pottier, Francis (Box 21, Folder 2255)
        - Potter, Philip Alford (Box 21, Folder 2256)
        - Poullart-des-Places, Claude-Francois (Box 21, Folder 2257)
        - Poysti, Nikolai (Box 21, Folder 2258)
        - Prasad, Krishna (Box 21, Folder 2259)
        - Pratt, George (Box 21, Folder 2260)
        - Pratt, Henry Barrington (Box 21, Folder 2261)
        - Pratt, Josiah (Box 21, Folder 2262)
        - Pradhan, Prem (Box 21, Folder 2263)
        - Price, Francis (Frank) Wilson (Box 21, Folder 2264)
        - Price (co-worker with Judson in Burma) (Box 21, Folder 2265)
        - Price, Roger (Box 21, Folder 2266)
        - Price, Thomas Frederick (Box 21, Folder 2267)
        - Price, W. Salter (Box 21, Folder 2268)
        - Priest, James M. (Box 21, Folder 2269)
        - Prip, Einar (Box 21, Folder 2270)
        - Probowinoto, Basoeki (Box 21, Folder 2271)
        - Prokhanov, Ivan Stephanovich (Box 21, Folder 2272)
        - Proksch, George (Box 21, Folder 2273)
        - Protten, Christian (Box 21, Folder 2274)
        - Quiroga, Vasco de (Box 21, Folder 2275)
        - Quaque, Philip (Box 21, Folder 2276)
        - Quinn, Edel Mary (Box 21, Folder 2277)
        - Raaflaub, Fritz (Box 21, Folder 2278)
        - Rabary (Box 21, Folder 2279)
        - Rafiringa, Paul (Box 21, Folder 2280)
        - Raban, John (Box 21, Folder 2281)
        - Rabinowitz, Josef Ben (Box 21, Folder 2282)
        - Rada, Martin de (Box 21, Folder 2283)
        - Rader, Paul (Box 21, Folder 2284)
        - Raaflaub, Fritz (Box 21, Folder 2284a)
        - Ragland, Thomas Gajetan (Box 21, Folder 2285)
        - Rahner, karl (Box 21, Folder 2286)
        - Railton, George Scott (Box 21, Folder 2287)
        - Raimondi, Timoleone (Box 21, Folder 2288)
        - Ramavai, Pandita (Box 21, Folder 2289)
        - Ramazzotti, Angelo Francesco (Box 21, Folder 2290)
        - Ramsey, Evelyn (Box 21, Folder 2291)
        - Ramseyer, F. (Box 21, Folder 2292)
        - Rankin, Melinda (Box 21, Folder 2293)
        - Ranson, Charles Wesley (Box 21, Folder 2294)
        - Rasa, Clorinda (Box 21, Folder 2295)
        - Rasalama, Rafaravavy (Box 21, Folder 2295a)
        - Rasoamanarivo, Victoire (Box 21, Folder 2296)
        - Ratisbonne, Marie-Theodore and Marie-Alphonse (Box 21, Folder 2297)
        - Rauch, Christian Henry (Box 21, Folder 2298)
        - Ravoux, Augustin (Box 21, Folder 2299)
        - Rawlinson, Frank (Box 21, Folder 2300)
        - Read, James (Box 21, Folder 2301)
        - Rebmann, Johannes (Box 21, Folder 2302)
        - Reed, George (Box 21, Folder 2303)
        - Reed, Mary (Box 21, Folder 2304)
        - Reekie, Archibald Brownlee (Box 21, Folder 2305)
        - Reeve, William (Box 21, Folder 2306)
        - Reginhar (Box 21, Folder 2307)
        - Regis, Jean Baptiste (Box 21, Folder 2308)
        - Rein-Wuhrmann, Anna (Box 21, Folder 2309)
        - Reichelt, Karl Ludvig (Box 21, Folder 2310)
        - Reid, Gilbert (Box 21, Folder 2311)
        - Reindorff, C. C. (Box 21, Folder 2312)
        - Reischauer, August K. (Box 21, Folder 2313)
        - Remigius of Reims (Box 21, Folder 2314)
        - Renner, Melchior (Box 21, Folder 2315)
        - Reynolds, Henry Robert (Box 21, Folder 2316)
        - Reynolds,Hiram Farnham (Box 21, Folder 2317)
        - Rhenius, Carl Theophilius Ewald (Box 21, Folder 2318)
        - Rhodes, Alexandre de (Box 21, Folder 2319)
        - Ricci, Matteo (Box 21, Folder 2320)
        - Rice, Benjamin (Box 21, Folder 2321)
        - Rice, Luther (Box 21, Folder 2322)
        - Richard, Timothy (Box 21, Folder 2323)
        - Richards, Henry (Box 21, Folder 2324)
        - Richards, William (Box 21, Folder 2325)
        - Richter, Enrique (Box 21, Folder 2326)
        - Richter, Julius (Box 21, Folder 2327)
        - Ricke, Jodoco (Box 21, Folder 2328)
        - Ricoldo da Monta Cruce (Box 21, Folder 2329)
        - Ridney, William (Box 21, Folder 2330)
        - Riedel, Johann Friedrich (Box 21, Folder 2340)
        - Riedemann, Peter (Box 21, Folder 2341)
        - Riggs, Elias (Box 21, Folder 2342)
        - Riggs, stephen Return (Box 21, Folder 2343)
        - Riis, Andreas (Box 22, Folder 2344)
        - Rijnhart, Susanna (Box 22, Folder 2345)
        - Ringeltaube, wilhelm Tobias (Box 22, Folder 2346)
        - Ritchie, John (Box 22, Folder 2347)
        - Roberts, Isachaar Jacox (Box 22, Folder 2348)
        - Robinson, John Alfred (Box 22, Folder 2349)
        - Robinson, William (Box 22, Folder 2350)
        - Rodgers, James Burton (Box 22, Folder 2351)
        - Roehl, Karl (Box 22, Folder 2352)
        - Rogers, Mary Josephine (Box 22, Folder 2353)
        - Rolland, Samuel (Box 22, Folder 2354)
        - Romero, Oscar Arnulfo (Box 22, Folder 2355)
        - Rommerskirchen, Johannes (Box 22, Folder 2356)
        - Ronne, B. F. (Box 22, Folder 2357)
        - Ronning, Halvor (Box 22, Folder 2358)
        - Roothaan, Johann Philipp (Box 22, Folder 2359)
        - Roots, Logan Herbert (Box 22, Folder 2360)
        - Rosenkranz, Gerhard (Box 22, Folder 2361)
        - Ross, John (Box 22, Folder 2362)
        - Ross, William (Box 22, Folder 2363)
        - Rossano, Pietro (Box 22, Folder 2364)
        - Rossel, Jacques (Box 22, Folder 2365)
        - Rossum, Willem Van (Box 22, Folder 2366)
        - Roth, Heinrich (Box 22, Folder 2367)
        - Rottler, J. P. (Box 22, Folder 2368)
        - Rouse, George Henry (Box 22, Folder 2369)
        - Rouse, Ruth (Box 22, Folder 2370)
        - Rovenius, Philippus (Box 22, Folder 2371)
        - Rowe, Phoebe (Box 22, Folder 2372)
        - Rowlands, John Francis (Box 22, Folder 2373)
        - Ruatoka (Box 22, Folder 2374)
        - Ruggieri, Michele (Box 22, Folder 2375)
        - Ruiz de Montoya, Antonio (Box 22, Folder 2376)
        - Rundle, Robert Terrill (Box 22, Folder 2377)
        - Ruiz, Manoel (Box 22, Folder 2378)
        - Russell, W. A. (Box 22, Folder 2379)
        - Rycroft, W. Stanley (Box 22, Folder 2380)
        - Ryland, John (Box 22, Folder 2381)
        - Sabatier, Ernst (Box 22, Folder 2382)
        - Sadrach (Box 22, Folder 2383)
        - Safford, Anna Cunningham (Box 22, Folder 2384)
        - Sahac (Box 22, Folder 2385)
        - Safdar, Ali (Box 22, Folder 2386)
        - Sahagun, Bernardino de (Box 22, Folder 2387)
        - Saint, Nathanael (Nate) (Box 22, Folder 2388)
        - Saint, Rachel (Box 22, Folder 2389)
        - Saker, Alfred (Box 22, Folder 2390)
        - Salazar, Francisco Domingo de (Box 22, Folder 2391)
        - Sale, Elizabeth (Box 22, Folder 2392)
        - Saminatha, Gnanaprasagar (Box 22, Folder 2393)
        - Samartha S(tanley J(edidiah) (Box 22, Folder 2394)
        - Sanders, John Oswald (Box 22, Folder 2395)
        - Salvado, Rosendo (Box 22, Folder 2397)
        - Samkange, Thompson Douglas (Box 22, Folder 2398)
        - San Victores, Diego Luis de (Box 22, Folder 2399)
        - Sandoval, Alonso de (Box 22, Folder 2400)
        - Santo Tomas, Domingo de (Box 22, Folder 2401)
        - Santori, Antonio (Box 22, Folder 2402)
        - Sandegren, Johannes (Box 22, Folder 2403)
        - Sarasin, Dorothy (Box 22, Folder 2404)
        - Sarasin, Karl (Box 22, Folder 2405)
        - Saravia, Adrianus (Box 22, Folder 2406)
        - Sargent, Douglas Noel (Box 22, Folder 2407)
        - Sargent, Edward (Box 22, Folder 2408)
        - Satti(Y)anathan, William Thomas and Anne (Devasahayam) (Box 22, Folder 2409)
        - Sava (Box 22, Folder 2410)
        - Sawabe, Paul (Box 22, Folder 2411)
        - Sawyerr, Harry Alphonse Ebun (Box 22, Folder 2412)
        - Schall Von Bell, Johann Adam (Box 22, Folder 2413)
        - Schauffler, William Gottlieb and mary Patt (Box 22, Folder 2414)
        - Schaefer, Alfons (Box 22, Folder 2415)
        - Scharer, Hans (Box 22, Folder 2416)
        - Schellenberg, Katharina L. (Box 22, Folder 2417)
        - Scherer, James A. B. (Box 22, Folder 2418)
        - Schereschewsky, Samuel Isaac Joseph (Box 22, Folder 2419)
        - Scherer, Heinrich (Box 22, Folder 2420)
        - Schiller, Karl Emil (Box 22, Folder 2421)
        - Schleiermacher, Friedrich Daniel Ernst (Box 22, Folder 2422)
        - Schlunk, Martin (Box 22, Folder 2423)
        - Schmelen, Johann Heinrich (Box 22, Folder 2424)
        - Scholtz, Odon (Box 22, Folder 2425)
        - Schomerus, Hilko wiardo (Box 22, Folder 2426)
        - Schon, Jakob Friedrich (Box 22, Folder 2427)
        - Schoenmakers, John (Box 22, Folder 2428)
        - Schreiber, August Wilhelm (Box 22, Folder 2429)
        - Schrenk, Elias (Box 22, Folder 2430)
        - Schreuder, Hans Paludan Smith (Box 22, Folder 2431)
        - Schmelzenbach, Elmer and Lula (Box 22, Folder 2432)
        - Schmemann, Alexander (Box 22, Folder 2433)
        - Schmid, Hans (Box 22, Folder 2434)
        - Schmidlin, Joseph (Box 22, Folder 2435)
        - Schmidt, Georg (Box 22, Folder 2436)
        - Schmidt, Wilhelm (Box 22, Folder 2437)
        - schnarre, john christian (Box 22, Folder 2438)
        - Schneder, David Bowman (Box 22, Folder 2439)
        - Schneller, Johann Ludwig (Box 22, Folder 2440)
        - Schultz, Stephan (Box 22, Folder 2441)
        - Schultze, Benjamin (Box 22, Folder 2442)
        - Schurhammer, Georg (Box 22, Folder 2443)
        - Schurmann (also churman), Johannes Adam (Box 22, Folder 2444)
        - Schuurman, Barend M. (Box 22, Folder 2445)
        - Schutte, Johannes (Box 22, Folder 2446)
        - Schutz, Paul (Box 22, Folder 2447)
        - Schwager, Friedrich (Box 22, Folder 2448)
        - Schwarz, Johann Gottlob (Box 22, Folder 2449)
        - Schwartz, Carl August Ferdinand (Box 23, Folder 2450)
        - Schwartz, Christian Friedrich (Box 23, Folder 2451)
        - Schweitzer, Albert (Box 23, Folder 2452)
        - Scofield, Cyrus Ingerson (Box 23, Folder 2453)
        - Scott, David Clement (Box 23, Folder 2454)
        - Scott, George (Box 23, Folder 2455)
        - Scott, Michael (Box 23, Folder 2456)
        - Scott, Peter Cameron (Box 23, Folder 2457)
        - Scranton, Mary (Box 23, Folder 2458)
        - Scranton, William F. (Box 23, Folder 2459)
        - Scudder, Ida S. (Box 23, Folder 2460)
        - Scudder, John (Box 23, Folder 2461)
        - Seagrave, Gordon S. (Box 23, Folder 2462)
        - Sedat, William and Betty (Box 23, Folder 2463)
        - Segura, Juan Baptista (Box 23, Folder 2464)
        - Sell, Edward (Box 23, Folder 2465)
        - Selwyn, George Augustus (Box 23, Folder 2466)
        - Semisi (Box 23, Folder 2467)
        - Serampore, Trio (Box 23, Folder 2468)
        - Sergeant, John (Box 23, Folder 2469)
        - Sergios of Valamo (Box 23, Folder 2470)
        - Serra, Junipero (Box 23, Folder 2471)
        - Seumois, Andre; V. (Box 23, Folder 2472)
        - Severinus (Box 23, Folder 2473)
        - Seward, Sara C. (Box 23, Folder 2474)
        - Seymour, William Joseph (Box 23, Folder 2475)
        - Shanahan, Joseph (Box 23, Folder 2476)
        - Sharkey, John Edmund and Ann Amelia (Box 23, Folder 2477)
        - Shattuck, Corinna (Box 23, Folder 2478)
        - Shaull, Richard (Box 23, Folder 2479)
        - Shaw, Archibald (Box 23, Folder 2480)
        - Shaw, Barnabas (Box 23, Folder 2481)
        - Shaw, William (Box 23, Folder 2482)
        - Sheen, Fulton J. (Box 23, Folder 2483)
        - Shedd, William Ambrose (Box 23, Folder 2484)
        - Shellabear, Wiliam (Box 23, Folder 2485)
        - Shelekoff, Grigori (Box 23, Folder 2486)
        - Shembe, Isaiah (Box 23, Folder 2487)
        - Shembe, Isaiah (Mention Son J. G. S.) (Box 23, Folder 2488)
        - Sheppard, William Henry and Lucy (Gantt) (Box 23, Folder 2489)
        - Shepherd, R.H.W. (Box 23, Folder 2490)
        - Shreve, Elizabeth (Box 23, Folder 2491)
        - Sibbes, Richard (Box 23, Folder 2492)
        - Shuck, J. Lewis and Henrietta (Box 23, Folder 2493)
        - Sibree, James (Box 23, Folder 2494)
        - Sigfrid (Box 23, Folder 2495)
        - Sihombing, Justinus (Box 23, Folder 2496)
        - Silva, Lourenco da (Box 23, Folder 2497)
        - Silveira, Goncalo da (Box 23, Folder 2498)
        - Simatupang, Tahi Bonar (Box 23, Folder 2499)
        - Simeon, Charles (Box 23, Folder 2500)
        - Simonton, Ashbel Green (Box 23, Folder 2501)
        - Simpson, A(lbert) B(enjamin) (Box 23, Folder 2502)
        - Simpson, William Wallace (Box 23, Folder 2503)
        - Singh, Bakht (Box 23, Folder 2504)
        - Skrefsrud, lars olsen (Box 23, Folder 2505)
        - Slater, Thomas Ebenezer (Box 23, Folder 2506)
        - Slessor, Mary Mitchell (Box 23, Folder 2507)
        - Smirnoff, Eugene (Box 23, Folder 2508)
        - Small, Ann Hunter (Box 23, Folder 2509)
        - Smith, Amanda Berry (Box 23, Folder 2510)
        - Smith, Arthur H. (Box 23, Folder 2511)
        - Smith, (A.C?) Stanley (Box 23, Folder 2512)
        - Smith, Edwin Williams (Box 23, Folder 2513)
        - Smith, Eli and Sarah Lanman Huntington (Box 23, Folder 2514)
        - Smith, George 1815-1871 (Box 23, Folder 2515)
        - Smith, George (Box 23, Folder 2516)
        - Smith, Henry Light (Box 23, Folder 2517)
        - Smith, John (Box 23, Folder 2518)
        - Smith, John Coventry (Box 23, Folder 2519)
        - Smith, Magtildt (Box 23, Folder 2520)
        - Smith, Oswald J(effrey) (Box 23, Folder 2521)
        - Smith, Wilfred Cantwell (Box 23, Folder 2522)
        - Smith, Stanley (Box 23, Folder 2523)
        - Smith, William (Box 23, Folder 2524)
        - Snow, Benjamin G. (Box 23, Folder 2525)
        - Soderblom, Nathan (Box 23, Folder 2526)
        - Soga, Minnie (Box 23, Folder 2527)
        - Soga, Tiyo (Box 23, Folder 2528)
        - Solano, Francisco (Box 23, Folder 2529)
        - Solages Gabriel-Henri-Jerome de (Box 23, Folder 2530)
        - Sonson, D. Phelipe (Box 23, Folder 2531)
        - Soper, Ann (Box 23, Folder 2532)
        - Soper, Edmund Davison (Box 23, Folder 2533)
        - Soto Fontanez, Santiago (Box 23, Folder 2534)
        - Spae, Joseph J. (Box 23, Folder 2535)
        - Spalding, Henry Harmon (Box 23, Folder 2536)
        - Spangenberg, August Gottlieb (Box 23, Folder 2537)
        - Spartas, Reuben (Box 23, Folder 2538)
        - Spaulding, Levi and Mary Chrystie (Box 23, Folder 2539)
        - Speer, Robert E(illiott) (Box 23, Folder 2540)
        - Spener, Philipp Jakob (Box 23, Folder 2541)
        - Spicer, William A(mbrose) (Box 23, Folder 2542)
        - Spieth, Jakob (Box 23, Folder 2543)
        - Spinola, Charles (Box 23, Folder 2544)
        - Spinner, Wilfred (Box 23, Folder 2545)
        - Spittler, Christian (Box 23, Folder 2546)
        - Springer, Helen (Box 23, Folder 2547)
        - Springer, John (Box 23, Folder 2548)
        - St. Andrews Seven (Box 23, Folder 2549)
        - Stach, Matthew (Box 23, Folder 2550)
        - Stahl Ferdinand Anthony (Box 23, Folder 2551)
        - Stallybrass, Edward (Box 23, Folder 2552)
        - Stam, John C. and Betty (Elizbeth Alden Scott) (Box 24, Folder 2553)
        - Stanley, Henry Morton (Box 24, Folder 2554)
        - Stanway, Alf (Box 24, Folder 2555)
        - Stauffacher, John and Florence (Box 24, Folder 2556)
        - Staunton, John Armitage Jr. (Box 24, Folder 2557)
        - Stavritsa, "Mama" (Box 24, Folder 2558)
        - Steidel, Florence (Box 24, Folder 2559)
        - Steere, Edward (Box 24, Folder 2560)
        - Steinkopf, Karl Friedrich Adolf (Box 24, Folder 2561)
        - Stephen (Box 24, Folder 2562)
        - Stephen (Charp) of Perm (Box 24, Folder 2563)
        - Stephen, Thomas (Box 24, Folder 2564)
        - Stern, Henry Aaron (Box 24, Folder 2565)
        - Stevens, Edwin (Box 24, Folder 2566)
        - Stevens, Jedediah D. (Box 24, Folder 2567)
        - Stevenson, Marion Scott (Box 24, Folder 2568)